{
 "football leagues":[
  { 
    "front": "england",
    "back": "premier league" 
  },
  { 
    "front": "spain", 
    "back": "la liga" 
  },
  { 
    "front": "germany", 
    "back": "bundesliga" 
  },
  { 
    "front": "italy",
    "back": "seria a" 
    },
  { 
    "front": "france",
    "back": "league 1" 
    }
],
"capitals" : [
  {
    "front": "West Bengal",
    "back": "kolkata"
  },
  {
    "front": "Assam",
    "back": "dispur"
  },
  {
    "front": "Karnataka",
    "back": "bengaluru"
  },
  {
    "front": "Uttar Pradesh",
    "back": "Lucknow"
  },
  {
    "front": "Chattisgarh",
    "back": "Raipur"
  }
]
}